A Guide to the Max Bergmann papers, Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research Scientific Staff FA001
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Declassifed Reports, 1940-1945; 5; 0.4 Cubic Feet
  - Literature Notes – Other Agents, undated, 1942-1944 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Literature Notes – W Agent, undated, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Lantern Slides, Undated; 6; 0.75 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  - Lantern slides (Box 17)
  - Lantern slides (Box 18)
  - Lantern slides (Box 19)